Tim Park

(714) 944-3085 | timpark0807@gmail.com | github.com/timpark0807 | U.S. Citizen

SUMMARY

Profile Software developer with 1 year of Full-Stack experience in the Finance industry.

Languages Python, GoLang, JavaScript, TypeScript

Other AWS, Django, React.js, Node.js, Flask, Git, SQL, NoSQL, HTML/CSS, OAuth, CI/CD Concepts Object-Oriented Programming, Data Structures & Algorithms, Microservices, REST API

EXPERIENCE

Accountant (Software Developer), Santa Barbara Auditor-Controller's Office

Aug 2017 - Present

- Developed a Django app to automate the monthly processing of \$225 million in sales tax revenue.
- Streamlined the FEMA labor cost claiming process (over \$4 million total) from 1 day to 10 min.
- Built a Django app that improved Special District audit and budget compliance by over 20%.
- Created an AWS service that reduced the delay in deposit notification from 2 days to 30 min.

Open Source Contributor, Django

Jun 2020 - Present

- Implemented a new feature, fixed bugs, wrote documentation, and improved test coverage.
- Participated in pull request reviews and collaborated with other developers to resolve tickets.

PROJECTS

Sales Tax App, Santa Barbara Auditor-Controller's Office

Nov 2019 - Present

- Used Django to automate 25 hours of monthly workload to < 15 min and reduce the error rate by 99%.
- Fetches external deposit CSV files, parses the response, and builds accounting transaction XMLs.
- · Owned all phases of delivery from stakeholder buy-in and system design to coding and debugging.

Inventory App, SneakrFlip.com

Mar 2020 – Present

- Built an inventory app using GoLang/React for reselling sneakers and other limited edition items.
- Implemented user authentication with OAuth bearer tokens and integrated Google social login.
- Deployed the backend/frontend on AWS EC2/S3 and implemented CI/CD with AWS Code Pipeline.

Finance News Service, Github.com/timpark0807

Feb 2020 - Present

- Built a Twitter microservice using Node.js to send users daily tweets with finance news articles.
- Deployed using AWS serverless architecture with Lambda, DynamoDB, SQS, and CloudWatch Events.
- Built a Chrome Extension in React, Reddit bot in Python, and GUI in Java with similar functionality.

Real Estate App, Reinvestify.com

May 2019 - Present

- Built a full-stack Flask app that generates reports on the profitability of real estate investments.
- Deployed the app on AWS, implemented a mortgage calculator, and introduced caching using Redis.

EDUCATION

Bachelors in Economics, University of California, Santa Barbara **AWS Certified Developer Associate,** Amazon Web Services, Cert #: ZGL37F0KMMF1QG5S

Jun 2017 May 2020